



Dhaka



01998419228



mohd.nazmussa kib@gmail.com



https://github.c om/Meeeeeow

#### **Skiils**

Languages & Styling tools: Python, JavaScript, C++, Java HTML, CSS, XML, Typescript, MUI,C#

# **Frameworks:**Bootstrap5, React, ASP.Net

**Backend:** Oracle, MSSQL,MySQL

# Nazmus Sakib

# **Career Objective**

Have the ability to work under pressure and deliver accordingly. Enthusiast for learning new frameworks or language. Have interest in frontend and full stack development and research works specially NLP and forecasting, pattern recognition-based works.

#### Education

# Monipur High School, Dhaka

• Science, GPA of 5.00

# Notre dame College, Dhaka

• Science, GPA of 5.00

# Ahsanullah University of Science and Technology, Dhaka

Computer Science and Engineering (CSE), CGPA of 3.31(Bachelors)

#### Bangladesh University of Engineering and Technology, Dhaka

Computer Science and Engineering (CSE), July, 2023 – Present (Masters)

# **Works**

Asp.net project (car retail website) semester:3.2
 GitHub link: <a href="https://github.com/Meeeeeow/ISD SD 3.2">https://github.com/Meeeeeow/ISD SD 3.2</a>

2. JavaScript & React JS Projects:

GitHub link: <a href="https://github.com/Meeeeeow/Mini-Projects-Front-End">https://github.com/Meeeeeow/Mini-Projects-Front-End</a>,

#### GitHub link(react):

- React redux CRUD: <a href="https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/react\_crud/react-crud">https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/react\_crud/react-crud</a>
- Wordle: <a href="https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/redux/react-wordle">https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/redux/react-wordle</a>
- E-commerce website with stripe integration: <a href="https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/cloth">https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/cloth</a> e-commerce
- Firebase and store with react:
   https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/authentication\_firebase/auth\_upload



- Rest API works: <a href="https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react">https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react</a>
- From Figma designs: <a href="https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/marketplace">https://github.com/Meeeeeow/refactored-react/tree/master/marketplace</a>
- 3. Python Projects

GitHub link: https://github.com/Meeeeeow/Python Projects

Machine learning & NLP: <a href="https://github.com/Meeeeeow/machine-learning">https://github.com/Meeeeeow/machine-learning</a>

4. Typescripts Projects

**GitHub link:** https://github.com/Meeeeeow/typescript-projects

# **Experience**

# Junior Software Developer – Radiant Data systems

Joining date – 1<sup>st</sup> February,2022 - current

Works with oracle, mirth, hl7 data, react, JavaScript. typescript

# Part-time Frontend Developer - BiznextIT

Joining date –13<sup>th</sup> April,2023 – 13<sup>th</sup> May

Worked with react, typescript, JavaScript, sharetribe marketplace api on an online learning platform

#### **Achievements**

 AutoAct: An Auto Labeling Approach Based on Activities of Daily Living in the Wild Domain (10<sup>th</sup> International Conference on Informatics, Electronics and Vision (ICIEV), 2021

Paper link: <a href="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/9564211">https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/9564211</a>

2. Appeared in IELTS - 10 Dec,2022
Reading- 9, Listening- 9, Speaking- 6, Writing- 6

Visit my website: <a href="https:/space-ravens.netlify.app/">https:/space-ravens.netlify.app/</a>

